hi spring fans welcome to another
嗨，春季粉丝们欢迎来到另一个
installment of spring tips and this look
春天技巧的分期付款和这个外观
we're gonna take a look at Jersey the
我们来看看泽西岛
sort of jsr 311 and jsr 339 reference
某种jsr 311和jsr 339参考
implementation for the jax-rs
jax-rs的实现
specification and particularly how it
规范，特别是它
integrates with spring boot to that oh
与 spring boot 集成到哦
right and of course spring boot to that
对的，当然还有 spring boot
oh is still early days yet so we're
哦，还很早，所以我们
gonna get a snapshot this is actually a
要获取快照，这实际上是
this is gonna have you know all these
这将让你知道所有这些
features will bubble into spring boot -
功能将进入 spring boot -
I know m4 which hasn't yet been released
我知道尚未发布的M4
and and we're just gonna look at how it
而且我们只是要看看它如何
works with some of the nice features of
具有以下功能
it how had it get going with it and so
它是如何发展的，所以
on so we're gonna build a new
这样我们就可以建立一个新的
application we're gonna call this the
应用程序，我们将其称为
customer service alright that's just our
好的客户服务就是我们的
application we're gonna use spring
我们将使用弹簧的应用程序
support for building we're gonna use the
支持建筑，我们将使用
rather than use the Lombok compile
而不是使用Lombok编译
compile time annotation processor will
编译时注释处理器将
use jersey itself now it's worth
现在使用球衣本身值得
mentioning that we have other there's
提到我们还有其他
another implementation of jax-rs it's
jax-rs的另一种实现是
supported here right so cxf let's see in
在这里支持，所以cxf让我们看看
spring boot proper spring 1.47 or 1.57
spring boot 适当的弹簧1.47或1.57
you'll see cxf alright but it's worth
您会看到cxf不错，但这值得
noting that we you know we keep support
指出我们知道您会继续提供支持
we integrate whatever we can Jack starts
我们整合一切，杰克开始
implementations and so for earlier
实现等等
versions there's two two there's at
版本有两个两个
least two versions right now and the
现在至少有两个版本，
early days of spring would to do 2.0
春季初期会做2.0
there's a there's Jersey so when you use
有一个泽西岛，所以当您使用
Jersey and we are going to use JPA when
泽西岛，我们将在以下情况下使用JPA
use h2 and I'm going to use the actuator
使用h2，我将使用执行器
right the actuator our set of endpoints
正确执行器我们的一组端点
that service information about the
有关的服务信息
application to serve the goals of
服务于目标的应用
observability so that you can understand
可观察性，以便您可以理解
what your system is doing and and I
您的系统在做什么，我
think that it will be enough us so let's
认为我们就足够了，所以让我们
go ahead and hit in generate that I'll
继续前进并生成我会的
give us a new project and we'll open
给我们一个新项目，我们将打开
this up in our IDE and again I've got a
在我们的IDE中，我再次有一个
convenient little script here now these
这些现在方便的小脚本
days I keep a little script you a
几天我给你写了个小剧本
customer service and that will open up
客户服务，这将打开
the application for us
对我们的申请
okay
好的
all right so we have now our customer
好的，所以我们现在有了我们的客户
service application we're gonna build a
服务应用程序，我们将构建一个
resource of course so I'm gonna go here
资源，所以我要去这里
will create a jax-rs rest endpoint so
将创建一个jax-rs rest端点，因此
we'll say insert a new class customer
我们会说插入一个新客户
resource and it's it's fair to assume
资源，这是公平的假设
that this customer resource is going to
该客户资源将用于
manage entities of type customers so
管理类型客户的实体，因此
we'll create that as well a new customer
我们还将创建一个新客户
and our customer will be a JPA entity
我们的客户将成为JPA实体
and we'll give it a private long ID and
我们会给它一个私人的长ID，
a private string name and the ID will
私有字符串名称和ID
say add ID at Jimmy value and we need
说添加Jimmy值的ID，我们需要
some getters and setters and so on so
一些吸气剂和二传手等等
easel and buck to generate all that and
画架和降压生成所有
make sure look at that work okay so now
确保好好看一下这项工作，现在
we we have the entity we need a
我们拥有我们需要的实体
repository right so that's create a
正确的存储库，以便创建一个
customer repository so that we have no
客户资料库，因此我们没有
need to fiddle with low level data
需要摆弄低水平的数据
management right that's just a function
只是功能的管理权
of Spring data and repositories but
Spring数据和存储库，但是
we've got now this we have an interface
我们现在有了这个，我们有一个界面
let's see there it's an interface now we
让我们看看现在有一个界面
can go back to our resource and we're
可以回到我们的资源，我们
gonna build a application that what is
会构建一个什么是
it it's gonna produce you know
它会产生你知道的
application JSON it's a rest endpoint
应用程序JSON是一个剩余端点
using jax-rs so I'm gonna use
使用jax-rs，所以我要使用
application JSON we're gonna map the
应用程序JSON，我们将映射
whole thing the whole class that will be
整个事情，整个班级
routed at forward slash customers so all
面向斜线客户，因此所有人
requests will be relative to that that
请求将相对于那个
URI there that that path we're gonna
URI就是我们要走的那条路
have one endpoint here that'll return a
在这里有一个端点将返回一个
single customer so let's try that a
单一客户，让我们尝试
single customer buy ID right so here we
单一客户购买ID对，所以在这里我们
are long ID I'm gonna give this a get
身份证很长，我要给它一个
mapping so it's gonna map to an HTTP GET
映射，因此它将映射到HTTP GET
request and we'll give it a path of
请求，我们将给它一条路径
parameter ID okay now that's gonna need
参数ID好的，现在需要
a path per am in the URL there okay and
网址中的每个路径都可以，并且
of course to do this we're going to need
当然要做到这一点，我们将需要
our repository our customer repository
我们的资料库我们的客户资料库
so let's inject that into the
所以我们将其注入
constructor and we'll return customer
构造函数，我们将回馈客户
repository at find by ID now of course
当然现在可以通过ID查找存储库
this is going to throw an exception it's
这将引发异常
an optional that we get back so it could
一个可选的，我们回来，所以它可以
throw an exception so we're gonna say
抛出一个异常，所以我们要说
it could be turn no rather until we need
除非我们需要
to do something with that so we need to
为此做些事情，所以我们需要
throw an exception we could say couldn't
抛出一个我们可以说不能的异常
find ID all right there's our simple
找到ID好吧，这很简单
example as simple as it gets
例子很简单
so now that's one endpoint I can also
所以现在这是一个端点，我也可以
imagine wanting to have another endpoint
想像一下要有另一个端点
here for all of the records so public
这里所有公开的记录
collection of customer customers and
客户和客户的集合
we'll just return this customer post
我们将退回此客户帖子
right find all alright now we have our
正确找到所有好了，现在我们有了
simple jax-rs
简单的jax-rs
endpoint but this is not you know itself
终结点，但这不是你自己
enough right we need to actually
我们需要足够的权利
configure one little tiny bit just to
配置一点点只是为了
make this work in the spring world so
使这个作品在春天的世界中变得如此
I'm gonna go back to our configuration
我要回到我们的配置
here our application and we'll just
在这里我们的应用程序，我们将只是
create a new configuration class called
创建一个名为的新配置类
Jersey configuration and there and we're
球衣配置以及我们
just gonna put anything that we need
会放任何我们需要的东西
related to making Jersey work right in a
与让Jersey正确运作有关
in a spring boot context so the first
在 spring boot 的背景下，所以第一个
thing that you absolutely need before
你之前绝对需要的东西
you can do anything else is a config
你可以做的其他事情就是配置
object a resource config and the
对象资源配置和
resource config is a you know kind of
资源配置是一种您知道的
the the central piece of the API
API的核心部分
actually so you return one of these and
实际上，所以您返回其中之一，
this actually activates a Springwood
这实际上激活了斯普林伍德
auto configuration but it's also where
自动配置，但这也是
we need to register components so we
我们需要注册组件，所以我们
need to teach Jersey about the beam that
需要教泽西关于光束
will be will be managed and we can do
将得到管理，我们可以做
this a couple of ways we could tell it
我们可以通过几种方式告诉它
just to scan the - to scan a certain
只是扫描-扫描某个
package try to set a set of packages we
包尝试设置一组我们的包
could look for certain classes we put in
可以寻找我们投入的某些课程
a packages etc we could do a lot of
一个包装等，我们可以做很多
different things here but we're just
这里有不同的事情，但我们只是
gonna register beans dynamically we're
要动态注册豆我们
gonna quit beans using spring and then
要用春季退出 Bean type ，然后
pass them their references to those
将他们的参考传递给他们
beans as we go so the so the first thing
豆，所以我们第一件事
that we need to do is to tell it where
我们需要做的就是告诉它在哪里
to find our customer resource so being a
寻找我们的客户资源，因此成为
customer resource and this will of
客户资源，这将
course depend on the customer repository
当然取决于客户资料库
and we'll say a new customer resource
我们会说一个新的客户资源
passing in the repository now that's a
现在通过存储库
inject that into the an endpoint here CR
将其注入此处的端点
and you'll say register CR very good so
你会说注册CR非常好
there's our first simple endpoint that's
我们的第一个简单终点是
just to start the application up and see
只是启动应用程序并查看
what we get now I'm gonna use the shell
我们现在得到的是我将使用外壳
here curl
这里卷曲
I'm sorry let's do a let's do HTTP
对不起，让我们做一个HTTP
localhost:8080 forward slash customers
本地主机：8080正斜杠客户
alright so there's our first endpoint
好了，这是我们的第一个终点
there's no data naturally I've got to
自然地我没有数据
insert some data so let's just create a
插入一些数据，让我们创建一个
you know for now so they have something
你现在知道所以他们有东西
with something with which to play we'll
玩的东西我们会
create some some sample data so data and
创建一些样本数据，这样数据和
we'll just have an application runner
我们将有一个应用程序运行程序
this is a callback interface and spring
这是一个回调接口和春天
boot naturally and it's an ideal place
自然启动，这是一个理想的地方
to put any kind of sample data or any
放置任何类型的样本数据或任何
kind of back-office initialization
后台初始化的一种
anything it happens outside the
它发生在外部的任何事情
traditional request response life cycle
传统的请求响应生命周期
of an application so we're gonna say
一个应用程序，所以我们要说
stream dot of a b c dot for each x c r
每个xcr的abc点的流点
dot save new customer passing an ol for
点保存新客户通过ol
the ID passing an x for the name and
传递x的ID作为名称，
this of course is a nice fit for lambdas
这当然很适合lambda
so we'll just use that it's a little bit
所以我们只用一点点
nicer and we can clean that up a little
更好，我们可以清理一点
bit alright there we are so we have our
有点好，我们在那里，所以我们有
sample data and if we were to run the
样本数据，如果我们要运行
application again which is what we're
再次申请，这就是我们
gonna do we can now hit the endpoint the
我们现在可以击中终点
the show and try again there we are
表演，然后再试一次
there's our few records so everything's
我们的记录很少，所以所有的
working out of the box we already we
开箱即用，我们已经
already have a working jack source
已经有工作的千斤顶源
application we can see the results here
应用程序，我们可以在这里看到结果
as expected everything's fine now let's
正如预期的那样，现在一切正常
talk about what happens if we go to that
谈论如果我们去那会发生什么
that second endpoint that at the
第二个端点
endpoint by ID so endpoint one all right
通过ID终结点，所以终结点一可以
okay we got our single record by its ID
好吧，我们通过ID获得了单条记录
now what happens if I go to endpoint six
现在如果我去端点6会发生什么
well of course I've only got three
当然，我只有三个
records so it's only it's gonna fail
记录，只有它会失败
right it's gonna throw a big fat Java
正确，它将抛出大量的Java
exception there so we need to to respond
有例外，所以我们需要回应
to that we need to care about the fact
我们需要关心的事实是
that that just happened and sending back
刚刚发生的事，然后发回
a big fat Java stack trace to the client
大量胖Java堆栈跟踪到客户端
while convenient isn't exactly a good
虽然方便并不完全是一件好事
form so we should take advantage of some
形式，所以我们应该利用一些
sort of generic mechanism so that we can
一种通用机制，以便我们可以
return a response a pop or response back
返回响应弹出或返回响应
to the client and remember most of our
给客户，并记住我们大多数
clients not gonna be human beings as we
客户不会像我们一样成为人类
are right now you know hitting the API
现在您知道点击了API
through a shell but instead other API
通过外壳但通过其他API
clients so we wouldn't want to have
客户，所以我们不想
something predictable and this is a good
可预测的东西，这是一个很好的
mechanism a good use for rather for the
该机制对于
exception mapper mechanism in checks
检查中的异常映射器机制
alright so I'm gonna say generic
好吧，我要说通用的
exception mapper implements exception
异常映射器实现异常
mapper and we're gonna map a legal
映射器，我们将映射一个合法的
argument exception right and so when we
论据例外权，所以当我们
when we have an exception thrown
当我们抛出异常时
anywhere in our resources we're gonna
我们资源中的任何地方
tend to it by returning just a response
通过返回一个响应来倾向于它
a a specific type of response response
特定类型的响应响应
server error I'm gonna have the entity
服务器错误，我要拥有实体
which is the body in this case the
在这种情况下是身体
exception string and then we'll just
异常字符串，然后我们将
build it and respond that respond with
建立并回应
that and we can just you know tell
那我们就可以告诉你
spring about this and inject that
关于这一点，注入
generic exception mapper
通用异常映射器
into our beam configuration here ok so
进入我们的光束配置
let's do that again
让我们再做一次
eeehm resource config register exception
eeehm资源配置注册异常
mapper here we are ok so now let's try
映射器在这里我们还好，所以现在让我们尝试
this again and go to the show
再一次去表演
all right let's try look at that
好吧，让我们尝试看看
couldn't find number six so we made a
找不到第六，所以我们做了一个
request but instead of getting the the
请求，但没有得到
big fat exception we got we had control
大脂肪异常，我们得到了控制
over the output and of course we were
超过产量，我们当然是
able to return hd500
能够返回hd500
we could do something more interesting
我们可以做一些更有趣的事情
you know we could say instead that we're
你知道我们可以说我们是
gonna return V and D errors which is a
将返回V和D错误，这是一个
pretty popular
很受欢迎
I'll be at non-standard representation
我将担任非标准代表
of errors there's a number of these
错误很多
things out there you can choose whatever
你可以选择任何东西
format you are encoding works for you
您编码的格式适合您
but for our purposes we have something
但出于我们的目的，我们有一些东西
so we know how we would do it right it
所以我们知道我们将如何做对
would create a an exception mapper
将创建一个异常映射器
alright so that's a pretty useful thing
好了，那是非常有用的事情
to do what else to wind it we've got a
做其他的事情来缠绕它，我们有一个
web application we built a REST API you
Web应用程序，我们为您构建了REST API
can see the REST API wasn't all that
可以看到REST API还不是全部
hard indeed none of this is all that
确实，这些都不是全部
hard a common concern when you move to
当您搬到
to a micro-services you know as you may
您可能知道的微服务
with jax-rs or spam you see or anything
看到j​​ax-rs或垃圾邮件或其他任何内容
else is observability I care about how
否则可观察性我在乎
this application is behaving and you
该应用程序的行为，你
know it doesn't matter which
知道哪一个都没关系
organization you talk to one thing is
你谈论一件事的组织是
surprisingly consistent it's the the
出奇的一致是
approach that they take as soon as a
他们尽快采取的方法
pager or rather pager Duty goes off
传呼机或更确切地说是传呼机
right something has to happen somebody
正确的事情一定要发生
gets woken up and roused to a computer
被唤醒并唤醒计算机
and has to respond and all the
并必须做出回应，
information that we can do all the
我们可以做的所有信息
information that we can serve surface to
我们可以提供服务的信息
support that effort that's that
支持那种努力
remediation process is valuable so
修复过程很有价值，因此
spring boot has you know long had the
spring boot 你知道多久了
the actuator an actuator is a very very
执行器执行器是非常非常
convenient set of endpoints that are
方便的一组端点
exposed there well first of all their
首先他们在那里暴露得很好
view agnostic so they've been exposed of
不可知论者，所以他们被暴露了
a rest and they can be exposed over JMX
休息，他们可以通过JMX公开
and so on but they're not bound to any
依此类推，但它们不受任何约束
one particular representation you can
您可以使用一种特定的表示形式
get the same information they used to
获得与过去相同的信息
build to gets the same information
建立以获取相同的信息
through the crash hub shell for example
例如通过防撞毂壳
and there's just a number of general
而且只有一些一般
ways to get this information well one
如何获得这些信息的方法之一
one thing that people have often
人们常有的一件事
clamored for was a they'd be able to the
他们大声疾呼，因为他们能够
ability to use the actuator in points
以点为单位使用执行器的能力
with a jacks or a simpler application
用千斤顶或更简单的应用程序
right the the actuator endpoints used to
正确的执行器端点
be tied at least insofar as they were
至少在一定程度上被捆绑
tied to an HTTP interface to spring MVC
绑定到HTTP接口以生成MVC
well that's no longer true in spring
好吧，春天不再如此
boot to do
启动做
we're we're reimagining the actuator
我们正在重新构想执行器
infrastructure to be sort of web runtime
Web运行时的基础架构
agnostic because we have to do that to
不可知的，因为我们必须这样做
support the sort of dichotomy between
支持之间的二分法
spring web flux are reactive web runtime
Spring Web Flux是反应性Web运行时
and spring MVC proper
和春季MVC适当
which is a servlet or at least servlet
这是一个servlet或至少是servlet
anchored web runtime because we have to
锚定Web运行时，因为我们必须
do that anyway we've we've also got the
无论如何，我们已经做到了
freedom to support things like jax-rs so
自由支持jax-rs这样的东西
we have the actuator in the classpath
我们在类路径中有执行器
all we need to do is to activate them so
我们需要做的就是激活它们
activator end points rather dot where
激活剂终点而不是点
the web endpoints default web
Web端点默认Web
and points dot
和点
oh did I get the wrong build I did build
哦，我做错了吗？
- snapshot okay never okay let's see
-快照好吧，永远不要吧，让我们看看
what we got here endpoints dot default
我们在这里得到的是端点点默认
that web-enabled equals true and we'll
启用网络等于true，我们将
run the application again there we go
再次运行应用程序
and we'll go to this show and make a
然后我们去看这个节目
request number one that's all working
要求所有的第一号
good now we go to application health no
好了，现在我们去应用程序健康否
application is just a default context
应用程序只是默认上下文
path but you can of course you can
路径，但你当然可以
configure that as you see fit so let's
按照您认为合适的方式进行配置，让我们
see what we got here come on come on
看看我们到这里来的来吧来吧
she'll there we are good so there's my
她会在那里我们很好所以那里是我的
there's my health endpoint all the
这是我的健康终点
configuration for that particular
该特定配置
application
应用
there's the env endpoint that shows me
有env端点向我显示
the system properties and environment
系统属性和环境
variables all that kind of stuff that I
变种我所有的东西
may want to debug configuration from one
可能想从一个调试配置
node to another that's that's you know
节点到另一个就是你知道的
Delta's important in particular that's
Delta特别重要的是
very useful what else we have we have a
非常有用，我们还有什么
whole number of different endpoints
不同端点的总数
which we can enumerate by just hitting
我们可以通过点击来枚举
the root application path so all these
根应用程序路径，所有这些
different endpoints that serve now to
现在可以服务于的不同端点
help us debug what the application is
帮助我们调试应用程序是什么
doing we've got the the usual suspects
我们有通常的嫌疑犯
see things that you may know from HP
查看您可能会从HP那里了解的事情
good application here and so on and so
很好的应用在这里等等
the JSON the syntax is a little
JSON的语法有点
different but that's part of the
不同，但这是
reworking for for a spring boot 2.0 as
为 spring boot 2.0重新加工
opposed to just jax-rs so now we've got
反对只是jax-rs，所以现在我们有了
that we've got a REST API
我们有一个REST API
are we done can we go to production well
我们完成了吗，我们可以顺利地进行生产吗
you know again I want to what we care
再次知道，我想关心我们
about in spring boot is production
大约在 spring boot 生产
worthiness right so this isn't much of a
值得，所以这不是很多
much of a service unless we have some
除非我们有一些服务
sort of security and obviously with
某种安全性，显然是
spring security you can do darn near
您可以在附近进行Spring Security 防护
anything so let's bring in spring
任何东西，让我们带入春天
security I
安全我
I didn't choose spring security back at
我没有选择Spring Security
the spring and newtralizer because I
春天和中和剂，因为我
forgot but it's not hard to bring in it
忘记了，但不难引入
so bring in spring boot starters
因此请带上 spring boot 靴
security and we're not going to spend
安全，我们不会花钱
too long here we're just gonna set up
我们在这里成立太久了
some security configuration right there
那里有一些安全配置
we are
我们是
yeah we are there's our configuration
是的，我们有我们的配置
and the first thing that we need to do
这是我们要做的第一件事
is to activate web security right we
是为了激活网络安全
need to activate spring security
需要激活弹簧安全性
remember that Jersey is just a servlet
记住泽西岛只是一个servlet
and a filter at the end of the day so
和一天结束时的过滤器
spring security is agnostic of any
Spring Security 性不可知
particular framework at some level right
某种程度上的特定框架
there is a point one where you can take
有一点可以采取
advantage of spring security and for
弹簧安全性和优势
example if using the MVC matters that's
例如，如果使用MVC很重要
a spring MVC ism but spring security
Spring MVC ism但Spring Security
works with the spring web flex coming in
与spring web flex一起使用
spring framework five it works with
与之兼容的Spring Framework 5
jax-rs it works with any web application
jax-rs它可与任何Web应用程序一起使用
at all that's why for the longest time
这就是为什么最长的时间
spring security was the number two most
Spring Security 防护是第二大安全防护
popular spring technology right after
紧随其后的流行弹簧技术
spring framework itself because even
Spring Framework本身，因为甚至
though you need spring to work with
虽然你需要春天来工作
spring security that is the libraries
Spring Security即库
themselves or sometimes dragon for
自己或有时是龙
spring security you don't have to use
您不必使用的Spring Security 防护
spring security with a spring based web
基于Spring的Web的Spring Security
application so for the last you know
申请，所以最后一次您知道
better part of a decade A+ where people
十年中A +的大部分时间
have had web applications and then when
拥有Web应用程序，然后何时
to secure your just pretend spring
确保你刚刚假装的春天
security that works very very very well
安全性非常好
very nicely right so we are going to
很好，所以我们要
integrate spring security and the first
整合Spring Security和First
thing that we want to do is just set up
我们要做的事情就是设置
some sort of authentication so let's
某种身份验证，所以让我们
create a user details Service bean
创建一个用户详细信息服务bean
custom user details service alright and
自定义用户详细信息服务还可以，
user detail services bean is just an
用户详细信息服务bean只是一个
object that spring security will
Spring Security 将反对的对象
delegate to when it wants to answer the
委托给它何时想要回答
question about who is making the request
有关谁在发出请求的问题
right now I want to validate that the
现在我想验证一下
request is coming from Josh or Rob or
请求来自Josh或Rob或
whoever right so we're just gonna use a
无论谁正确，我们都将使用
new in-memory user details manager which
新的内存中用户详细信息管理器
is in turn going to accept a collection
反过来将接受一个集合
of user details so let's say arrays dot
用户详细信息，所以说数组点
as list and we're going to create a
作为列表，我们将创建一个
little convenient method here private
这里私人的小方便方法
static user details user string user and
静态用户详细信息用户字符串user和
we're gonna say that there's gonna be
我们会说会有
some roles and we'll say we user dot
一些角色，我们将说用户点
with username user we're gonna use the
使用用户名用户，我们将使用
same default password just a demo after
相同的默认密码只是一个演示之后
all but obviously in a real thing you
所有人，但显然是一件真实的事情，
talk to a database or you wouldn't even
与数据库对话，或者甚至都不会
use you you wouldn't even use the user
使用你，你甚至不会使用用户
detail service you'd use some sort of
您将使用某种细节服务
authentication manager that talks to
与之对话的身份验证管理器
whatever back in identity provider
身份提供商提供的任何支持
you've got but in our case so I just
你有，但就我们而言，我只是
wanna establish that you can use jax-rs
想确定您可以使用jax-rs
with spring security quite easily so
Spring Security 性相当容易
we're gonna create a just a simple use
我们将创建一个简单的用法
of detail service that knows about to
的详细服务
use
采用
user one is gonna be mr. winch mr. Rob
用户一将是先生。绞车先生抢
winch the lead of spring security
绞车牵动弹簧安全
naturally so he'll be an admin as well
自然地，所以他也将成为管理员
as user and I will be there
作为用户，我将在那里
that's just a user right so just a user
那只是用户权限，所以只有一个用户
one rule for me two for him okay
一个规则对我来说两个对他好
and pass that in there there we are
并将其传递到那里
there's our collection of users and our
有我们的用户群和我们的
custom user details service now this is
自定义用户详细信息服务，现在是
interesting in of itself but I want to
本身很有趣，但我想
also secure the applicator oh I want to
还可以保护涂抹器哦，我想
I've got security on the class map but I
我的班级地图上有安全性，但我
need to lock down access to the
需要锁定对
different endpoints and I want to make
不同的端点，我想
sure that you have to be at least
确保您至少要
authenticated to talk to any of these
经过身份验证可以与其中任何一个进行交谈
different endpoints so let's extend here
不同的端点，所以让我们在这里扩展
the web security configure a doctor and
网络安全配置一名医生，
override the HTTP security so there is
覆盖HTTP安全性，因此
this I'm gonna say HTTP dot H TV basic
我要说的是HTTP dot H TV basic
will support HT basic security and
将支持HT基本安全性并
authorize requests any requests dot you
授权请求任何请求点您
know and then that's it actually
知道，然后就是这样
that'll be that's enough to get
那就足够了
something useful so let's now try this
一些有用的东西，让我们现在尝试一下
again okay and we'll go back to the
再次好吧，我们将回到
shell here we are
壳我们在这里
alright so let's see HTTP - for verbose
好吧，让我们看一下HTTP-详细
okay
好的
oops
哎呀
there's some configuration issue no any
有一些配置问题
requests not authenticated okay so we'll
请求未通过身份验证可以，因此我们将
start that again go to the go to the
重新开始，转到转到
show-off application okay good
炫耀应用还可以
it says full authentication is required
它说需要完全认证
to access this resource fair enough
足够公平地访问此资源
let's try it now with a off J long whoa
让我们现在尝试关闭J long哇
day long password alright so there's the
好一天的密码，所以有
data now let's try it with Rob there's
数据，现在让我们与Rob一起尝试
the data again good stuff alright that
数据再次是好东西
seems to be working but let's say that
似乎正在工作，但可以说
instead I want to I want to require that
相反，我想要我想要
every every endpoint be authenticated
每个端点都经过身份验证
but I want to require specifically that
但我想特别要求
the the customers endpoints the admin
客户终结管理员
only right so I'm gonna use an ant
只对，所以我要用一只蚂蚁
matcher and I'll say customers customers
匹配器，我会说客户客户
forward slash dot has role admin ok and
正斜杠具有管理员角色，并且
we'll leave it like that otherwise it's
我们会像那样离开，否则
we're just creating a very specific
我们只是在创建一个非常具体的
matcher forever for that one endpoint
永远匹配那个端点
one set of end points and then otherwise
一组端点，然后否则
everything else including the actual
其他一切，包括实际
endpoints has to be authenticated so
端点必须经过身份验证
let's restart the application and we'll
让我们重新启动应用程序，然后
go back to the show here now he's got
回到这里，现在他有
access to that no problem go back to me
进入那没问题再回到我身边
regular user no problem what about
普通用户没问题
customers so I should not have access to
客户，所以我不应该访问
this endpoint right access is denied
此端点权限访问被拒绝
strictly I can go back to Rob here ok
严格来说，我可以回到罗布这里
there's Robin I'm gonna go back to the
罗宾，我要回去
customers endpoint for him and you'll
客户为他服务，您将
see that he has actually access to the
看到他实际上有权访问
data so in this example we've got spring
数据，所以在此示例中，我们有了春天
security locking out requests that are
安全性将请求锁定
unauthenticated maybe we've got
未经认证的也许我们有
authorization in place we've configured
授权已配置到位
authorization
授权书
one last bridge however is I want my
最后一座桥是我想要我的
application I want my way I want my a
我想要我的方式我想要我的
resource my jax-rs application aware of
资源我的jax-rs应用程序意识到
the authentication right I want to be
我想成为的验证权
able to dereference or interrogate the
能够取消引用或审讯
the authenticated principle and this
认证原则和本
requires a little bit of bridge work so
需要一点桥梁工作，所以
we're gonna write a little bit of code
我们要写一点代码
here to bridge the security context
在这里桥接安全上下文
mechanism from spring security with that
弹簧安全的机制
of jax-rs which turned out not to be all
的jax-rs证明不是全部
that difficult to do so we need to
很难做到，所以我们需要
create a filter that looks like this
创建一个看起来像这样的过滤器
it's a a filter c class bridging
这是一个过滤器c类桥接
security filter and it's going to
安全过滤器，它将
implement a container request filter and
实现一个容器请求过滤器并
the job here it's a you know it's a
这是一个工作，你知道这是一个
jax-rs mechanism our job here is to plug
jax-rs机制，我们的工作是插入
in a security context object right so
在安全上下文对象中正确
that security context object is what's
该安全上下文对象是什么
going to be on the request when the the
将在请求时
jax-rs can resource processes the
jax-rs可以资源处理
incoming request so we need to put that
传入请求，因此我们需要输入
it on there and it's not such a big deal
它在那里，这没什么大不了的
right we can actually create a very
对，我们实际上可以创建一个非常
simple one that bridges to our spring
简单的桥梁，通往我们的春天
security security context so there's
安全性安全上下文
actually a swing security context that
实际上是一个摇摆的安全上下文
keeps a pointer that we can get access
保留一个我们可以访问的指针
to for them from a thread local there's
从本地线程那里为他们
a static low cup method that we can use
我们可以使用的静态低杯法
if you're using spring MVC you can just
如果您使用的是Spring MVC，则可以
inject that authentication principle
注入认证原则
into spring MVC controller handlers and
进入Spring MVC控制器处理程序并
there's a similar mechanism in jax-rs so
jax-rs有类似的机制，所以
once we get this working we can go you
一旦我们完成这项工作，我们就可以帮助您
know we should be able to rewrite this
知道我们应该能够重写这个
code and take advantage of that
代码并利用它
authenticate principle by saying at
通过在
context security context context right
上下文安全上下文上下文权限
so all I'm going to do now is I'm going
所以我现在要做的就是
to log out information about the
注销有关
requesting a user private final log log
请求用户私人最终日志日志
equals log factory get log get class
等于日志工厂获取日志获取类
there we are okay so now we'll put that
那里我们还好，所以现在我们把
there and we'll say this dot log info
在那里，我们将说这个点日志信息
and we're gonna say context dot get user
我们要说上下文点吸引用户
principal get name was here all right so
校长得到名字就可以了
there's our authenticated context we
有我们经过身份验证的上下文
should be able to print that out when
应该能够将其打印出来
the request comes in because it'll be
该请求进入，因为它将
secured right you won't be able to get
担保权，您将无法获得
to this end point without going through
到这个终点而无需经历
spring security which will in turn
Spring Security ，这将反过来
populate this security context so now
填充此安全上下文，所以现在
let's go back to our filter here
让我们回到这里的过滤器
we need to write a custom security
我们需要编写自定义安全性
context implementation so private static
上下文实现，所以私有静态
class bridging security context
类桥接安全上下文
implements security context all right
可以实现安全上下文
there's our security context contract
有我们的安全上下文合同
and then the contract is fairly
然后合同是公平的
straightforward so we're going to inject
简单明了，所以我们要注入
the spring security context here I'm
我在这里的Spring Security 上下文
gonna call it spring so that I have a
要叫它春天，以便我有一个
even easy time of figure out which one
甚至很容易找出哪一个
is which and we need information about
是哪个，我们需要有关的信息
the URL that's being used to make the
用于制作
request so I'm gonna inject the URI info
请求，所以我要注入URI信息
from my my request in the filter right
根据我在过滤器中的要求
so we can actually use the the the
所以我们可以实际使用
Jack's runtime Jersey in this case to
杰克的跑步球衣在这种情况下
inject that there so let's see our
注入那里，让我们看看我们的
filter will need that we're gonna say at
过滤器将需要我们在
context your I info alright there's this
上下文您我的信息还可以
and now we'll say new bridging security
现在我们要说新的桥接安全性
filter and the security filter or rather
过滤器和安全过滤器，或更确切地说
no bridging security context and the
没有桥接安全上下文，并且
context is going to need the spring
情境将需要春天
security context so we'll say security
安全上下文，所以我们说安全
context holder dot get context no
上下文持有者点获取上下文否
problem
问题
this that URI info all right so there's
这个URI信息没问题，所以
our bridging security context now let's
我们的桥接安全上下文现在让我们
implement this security context itself
本身实现此安全上下文
so spring dot authentication done spring
所以春天点认证完成春天
dot get authentication we could
点获取身份验证，我们可以
implement this a number of different
实施一些不同的方法
rays different ways but I think the
以不同的方式发出光线，但我认为
simplest might just be to look at the
最简单的可能只是看一下
authorities and see if any of those
当局，看看是否有任何
match so let's try that ok so well say
匹配，让我们尝试确定
dot any mapping or steamed out any
点任何映射或蒸出任何
mapping any match rather GA it's a
映射任何匹配而不是GA，这是一个
granted authority object that has a
授予的授权对象，具有
pointer to a Authority and we're gonna
指向权威的指针，我们将
see if it contains they straight the
看看是否包含它们直
role s okay so there's that and finally
角色还可以，所以有，最后
we'll say URI info dot get absolute path
我们会说URI信息点获得绝对路径
that starts with its GPS I have to
从它的GPS开始，我必须
tenacious vs request we're gonna say
顽强vs请求，我们要说
it's secure so that seems fine spring
这很安全，所以春天似乎很好
security authentication all right that's
安全身份验证没关系
our custom scheme there and otherwise
我们那里的自定义方案，否则
that seam
那缝
to be okay so we've rewritten our rest
没关系，所以我们重写了其余部分
endpoint our customer service resource
终结我们的客户服务资源
accordingly to to inject that context
相应地注入上下文
let's now go back to the shell and see
现在让我们回到外壳上，看看
what happened so customers forward slash
发生了什么，所以客户大胆砍
one okay we got the data back and if I
好的，我们取回了数据，如果我
go to the run
去跑步
I'll put there there we are it says Rob
我会放在那里，罗布说
Lynch was here so with that we've just
林奇在这里，我们只是
looked at how to create a jak source
看了如何创建一个jak源
application using Jersey and spring boot
球衣和 spring boot 的应用程序
to that o we took advantage of the new
为此，我们利用了新的
actuator machinery integration in spring
弹簧执行器机械集成
boot to zero we we looked at how to take
开机至零，我们研究了如何服用
advantage of of spring security and
弹簧安全性的优势和
application and everything else should
应用程序以及其他所有内容
be fairly straightforward this is just a
很简单，这只是一个
spring good application it's using JP
春天很好的应用程序，它使用JP
and hibernate and you know all that
冬眠，你知道的一切
other stuff we're getting spring data
我们正在获取 spring data 的其他内容
and the mix it's a so-called fat jar so
混合起来就是所谓的胖子
you can just do - jar - to run the
你可以做-jar-运行
application to deploy it so in every
应用程序来部署它
other way it's just what you expect but
换句话说，这正是您的期望，但是
it just works very nicely with them with
它与他们一起很好地工作
jax-rs
杰克斯
so with that my friends thank you so
所以我的朋友们非常感谢你
much for watching and we'll see you next
收看很多，我们下次见
time
时间
you
您